Guide to the Thornton Wilder Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1908-1985; Series I; 27.11; (67 boxes)
  - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE
    - Carroll, David, 1963-65 (Box 28, Folder 674)
    - Carroll, Walter, 1975-77 (Box 28, Folder 675)
    - Cather, Willa, 1938, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 676)
    - Catherman, Terry, 1954-57, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 677-679)
    - Cecil, David, 1956 Nov 21 (Box 29, Folder 680)
    - Centre Theatre Group, 1966-69 (Box 29, Folder 681)
    - Century Club, 1965-66 (Box 29, Folder 682)
    - Channing, Carol, 1967-87, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 683-685)
      See also: Charles Lowe, Box 47, folder 1249
    - Charles Scribner's Sons, 1963-68 (Box 29, Folder 686)
    - Chase, Marian Tyler, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 687)
    - Chatham College, 1964-65 (Box 29, Folder 688)
    - Chou, Lily, 1968-72, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 689)
    - Circle in the Square, 1959-75 (Box 29, Folder 690)
      See also: Theodore Mann, Box 48, folder 1284
    - Cisney, Marcella
      See: Marcella Schnitzer, Box 54, folder 1516-1517
    - Clark, Kenneth, Sir
      See: Heit & Rothenberg, Box 341, folder 1039-1048
    - Clemens, Cyril, 1962-73, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 691)
    - Clements, Robert, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 692)
    - Clift, Montgomery, 1943-55, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 693)
    - Clinchy, Everett, 1963-68 (Box 29, Folder 694)
    - Clurman, Harold
      See: Group Theatre, Box 36, folder 936
    - Cockerell, Sydney, 1955-55 (Box 29, Folder 695)
      With: letter to Isabel Wilder from Dorothy Hawksley, 1954 Oct 4
    - Coe College, 1970-75, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 696)
    - Coffin, Catherine, 1947-74, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 697)
    - Cohen, Harriet, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 698)
      With: Correspondence with Rubenstein, Nash concerning a bequest from Cohen to Wilder, 1968
    - Cohn, Janet, 1942-62, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 699)
    - Colbert, Robert, 1975 Jan 15 (Box 29, Folder 700)
    - Cole, Nancy, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 701)
    - Colefax, Michael, 1974, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 702)
    - Colefax, Sybil, 192[?]-41 (Box 29, Folder 703-707)
      Includes letter from Max Beerbohm to Colefax, 1926 Apr 23, annotated by Wilder: "Max Beerbohm. For the scrapbook."
    - Colefax, Sybil, 1942-50, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 708-714)
    - Coleman, Sister Anne Gertrude, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 715)
    - College Center of the Finger Lakes, 1962-63 (Box 30, Folder 716)
    - Colin, Saul, 1954, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 717)
    - Collins, David J., 1968 (Box 30, Folder 718)
    - Colony, Horatio, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 719)
    - Colum, Mary, 1940 Nov 7 (Box 30, Folder 720)
      With: letter to Wilder from the Bank of the Manhattan Company, 1940
    - Columbia University, 1963-70 (Box 30, Folder 721)
    - Columbia University Oral History Project, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 722)
    - Comediantes Club, 1964-66 (Box 30, Folder 723)
    - Communaunté Theatrealé, 1965-66 (Box 30, Folder 724)
    - Connelly, Marc, 1935 Feb 2 (Box 30, Folder 725)
    - Conrad, Oona, 1967 Mar 10 (Box 30, Folder 726)
    - Cons, Louis, 1928 (Box 30, Folder 727)
    - Contemporary Authors, 1965-66 (Box 30, Folder 728)
    - Copland, Aaron, 1966, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 729)
    - Corfman, Eunice, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 730)
    - Coriolis-Eastman, Therese, 1951-60, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 731)
    - Cornell, Katharine, 1932, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 732)
    - Cornyn, Stan, 1961, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 733)
    - Corrigan, Robert, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 734)
    - Cotkin, Morris, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 735)
    - Coward-McCann, Inc., 1928-68 (Box 30, Folder 736-739)
    - Coward, Noel, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 740)
      Includes third-party correspondence sent on to Wilder by Coward-MacCann
    - Cowley, Malcolm, 1956-78, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 741)
      With: "The Red Wagon," typescript of poem by Cowley, 1975
    - Craven, Frank, 1938 Jan 8 (Box 31, Folder 742)
    - Craig, Bill, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 743)
    - Crawford, Cheryl, 1956-66, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 744)
    - Criterion Books, 1956-67 (Box 31, Folder 745)
    - Cubeta, Paul, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 746)
    - Cukor, George, 1967 Feb 25 (Box 31, Folder 747)
    - Cunningham, Dennis Y., 1965-70 (Box 31, Folder 748)
    - Curtius, Ernst Robert, 1949, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 749)
    - "D" general, 1927-75, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 750-753)
    - Dahlberg, Gilda, 1961-75, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 754)
    - Dakin, Rodney G., 1963-65 (Box 31, Folder 755)
    - Dalton, Jack, 1964-65 (Box 31, Folder 756)
    - Damon, S. Foster, 1941 May 29 (Box 31, Folder 757)
    - Dana, J. Dwight, 1928-65 (Box 31, Folder 758-759)
    - Daniels, Mabel, 1962-65, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 760)
      See also: Wiggin & Dana, Boxes 62-63, folders 1728-1760
    - Davidson, Louise, 1964-68, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 761)
    - Davies, Robertson, 1959 Mar 18 (Box 31, Folder 762)
    - Day, George Parmly, 1931, 1952 (Box 31, Folder 763)
      With: note from Day to Yale University Library, 1952
    - De Bosis, Lauro, 1929, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 764)
      With: copy of poem, "Ciascun mattino sugli azzurri monti" dated 1925 Apr 14, in Isabel Niven Wilder's hand
    - De Bosis, Lilian, 1948, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 765)
    - Deckelman, Robert, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 766)
    - De Fillipo, Eduardo, 1971-74, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 767)
    - Delaney, William Adams, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 768)
    - De Mille, Agnes, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 769)
    - Demme, Günter-Klaus, 1962-64 (Box 31, Folder 770)
    - Dershaw, D. David, 1964-67 (Box 31, Folder 771)
    - De Sica, Vittorio, 1949-57, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 772)
    - The Dial, 1918 Aug 18 (Box 31, Folder 773)
    - Dial Press, Inc., 1963 (Box 31, Folder 774)
    - Dickinson College, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 775)
    - Diedenhofen, Karl, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 776)
    - Dodd, Martha, 1933-34 (Box 31, Folder 777)
    - Dodd, Mead & Company, Inc, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 778)
      With: photograph of Dodd in group, 1934 Nov
    - Dodd, Thomas J., 1963 Dec 12 (Box 31, Folder 779)
    - Dodson, Robert, 1957-63, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 780-781)
      With: typescript of poem, "Covered Bridge," and journal entries by Dodson
    - Doubleday & Co., 1965-69, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 782)
    - Donaldson, Scott, 1969, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 783)
    - Drama Survey, 1962-63 (Box 31, Folder 784)
    - Dramatists' Play Service, 1944 Feb (Box 32, Folder 785)
    - Draper, Ruth, 1931-48, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 786-787)
      With: copy of letter by Lauro de Bosis, 1930 Dec 28, and typescript of "Lo spirito de l'oro," 1931
    - Du Bos, Charles, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 788)
    - Dublin Gate Theatre
      See: Christine Longford, Box 46, folder 1239
    - Dugan, Claire, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 789)
    - Duhrssen, Margaret, 1967-69 (Box 32, Folder 790)
    - Dunbar, Margaret, 1966-70 (Box 32, Folder 791)
    - Dunnam, Maxie D., 1964 (Box 32, Folder 792)
    - Durnell, Hazel B., 1969-83, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 793)
    - "E" general, 1936-75, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 794-796)
    - E. P. Dutton & Co., 1965 (Box 32, Folder 797)
    - Eberhart, Richard, 1951 Oct 11 (Box 32, Folder 798)
    - Edelstein, Jerome Melvin, 1954-68, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 799-800)
    - Edelstein, Eleanor
    - Edinburgh Festival Society Ltd., 1954-55 (Box 32, Folder 801)
    - Edmunds, John
      See: Marcia Nardi, Box 49, folder 1346-1347
    - Educational Laboratory Theatre Project, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 802)
    - Eisenhower, Milton
      See: Planned Parenthood, Box 51, folder 1415
    - Einstein, Albert, 1938 Aug 12 (Box 32, Folder 803)
    - Ely, John T. A., 1944-45 (Box 32, Folder 804)
    - Emery, George, 1962-63 (Box 32, Folder 805)
      See also: Marshall Bean, Box 15, folder 377
    - English-American Library, 1962-63 (Box 32, Folder 806)
    - Enters, Angna, 1956-63, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 807)
      With: costume drawing by Enters
    - Equity Library Theatre, 1945-70 (Box 32, Folder 808)
    - Ernst, Morris L., 1963-66 (Box 32, Folder 809)
    - Esquire, 1962-75 (Box 32, Folder 810)
    - Etcovitch, Barbara, 1972-74 (Box 32, Folder 811)
    - Evans, Edith, Dame, 1938-50, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 812-813)
    - Evans, Richard, 1938-45 (Box 32, Folder 814)
    - Evarts, John, 1951-75 (Box 32, Folder 815)
    - "F" general, 1930-75, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 816-818)
    - Fadiman, Regina, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 819)
    - Fallon, Thomas, 1961-62 (Box 33, Folder 820)
    - Farrar, John C., 1954 Feb 3 (Box 33, Folder 821)
    - Farrar, Margaret, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 822)
    - Farrar, Straus & Giroux, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 823)
    - Farrow, Mia, 1970-87, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 824-825)
      See also: Andre Previn, Box 51, folder 1432
      With: photographs of Farrow's children, 1983
    - Farwell, Byron, 1956-73, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 826)
    - Faulkner, William
      See: People-to-People Program, Box 51, folder 1402
    - Fay, Bernard, 1962 Dec 7 (Box 33, Folder 827)
    - Feinberg, Charles E., 1962 (Box 33, Folder 828)
    - Felty, Ronald, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 829)
    - Fenwick, Joseph C., 1961-75, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 830)
    - Ffennell, Sonja, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 831)
    - Ffolkes, David, 1947-49 (Box 33, Folder 832)
    - Fisher, Betty W., 1965, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 833)
    - Fiske, Irving, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 834)
    - Fitts, Norman, 1923-25, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 835)
      Includes: S4N Issue 33, year 6, with letter to TNW
    - Fitzgerald, F. Scott, 1928 Mar 23 (Box 33, Folder 836)
    - Fitzgerald, Geraldine, 1946, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 837)
    - Fitzgerald, Zelda, [1928 Apr] (Box 33, Folder 838)
    - Flanner, Janet, 1967 Mar 23 (Box 33, Folder 839)
    - Folster, George Thomas, 1956-57 (Box 33, Folder 840)
    - Fontanne, Lynn
      See: Alfred Lunt, Box 47, folder 1258
    - Ford, Ruth, 1974 Mar 25 (Box 33, Folder 841)
    - Foresman, Grace, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 842)
    - Foss, Lukas, 1953-67 (Box 33, Folder 843)
    - Foster, J. J., 1942-75, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 844-846)
    - Four Quarters, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 847)
    - Fox, Carol, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 848)
      With: photocopy of letter to Louise Talma from Julius Rudel, 1965
    - France, Richard, 1968-72 (Box 33, Folder 849)
    - Franklin and Marshall College, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 850)
    - Franklin, Miriam, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 851)
    - Franklin Publications, 1953-64, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 852)
    - Fraser, Donald M., 1966 (Box 33, Folder 853)
    - Frederick Ungar Publishing Company, 1966-70 (Box 33, Folder 854)
    - Free Europe Committee, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 855)
    - Freedley, George, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 856)
      See also: New York Public Library, Box 49, folder 1361
    - Freedman, Harold, 1932-62 (Box 33, Folder 857)
    - French, Norman, 1968-80 (Box 33, Folder 858)
      With: article by French on Wilder from Americans in Paris, 1920-1939, 1980
    - Freud, Esti, 1973 Nov 4 (Box 33, Folder 859)
    - Freud, Sigmund, 1936-38 (Box 33, Folder 860)
      With: letter to Wilder from Ernst Waldinger, 1938
    - Freund, Giséle, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 861)
    - Friel, Brian, 1964 Apr (Box 33, Folder 862)
    - Friends of Bruce Simonds, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 863)
    - Frulla, Guelfo, 1957-64, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 864)
    - Fuller, Henry B., 1928 (Box 33, Folder 865)
    - Fuller, Buckminster, 1943-73 (Box 33, Folder 866)
      With: "World Map on Dymaxion Projection"
    - Fulner, David, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 867)
    - "G" general, 1945-75, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 868-871)
    - Galerie "Im Erker", 1962-63 (Box 34, Folder 872)
    - Gallimard (Firm), 1945-51 (Box 34, Folder 873)
    - Galinsky, G. Carl, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 874)
    - Gallup, Donald, 1961-74, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 875)
    - Gaslight Players, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 876)
    - Gassner, John, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 877)
    - Gerson, Noel, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 878)
    - Gex, Emile J., 1936 (Box 34, Folder 879)
    - Gielgud, John, 1942-66, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 880)
    - Gilbert, Beatrice Joy, 1973-75 (Box 34, Folder 881)
    - Gilbert, Mack J., 1962 (Box 34, Folder 882)
    - Gimbel, Richard, 1930 Jul 24 (Box 34, Folder 883)
    - Ginn and Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 884)
    - Girlhaven, Inc., 1963-66 (Box 34, Folder 885)
    - Gish, Lillian, 1947-86, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 886)
    - Glasgow, Mary, 1946-66, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 887)
    - Glamour, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 888)
    - Glasheen, Adeline, 1951-74, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 889-891)
    - Glenn, C. Leslie, 1923-75, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 892-898)
      With: letter to Glenn from William Thomas Heath, 1976
    - Glenn, Maggie, 1953-56 (Box 35, Folder 899)
      With: two letters to Wilder from Anne Taylor, 1954
    - Glowacki, Stanley, 1975 Jul 18 (Box 35, Folder 900)
    - Goethe House, 1964-65 (Box 35, Folder 901)
    - Goldstein, Malcolm, 1962-83 (Box 35, Folder 902-903)
    - Goldstone, Richard, 1954-71, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 904-907)
      Includes third-party correspondence to Goldstone about his proposed biography of Wilder; also includes note from "Bob H." to Goldstone announcing that Wilder has been nominated for the Nobel, 1969
    - Gonzalez, Fernando, 1941 (Box 35, Folder 908)
      With: undated typescript, "La Santa Rusia"
    - Goodbody, Douglas, 1943-75 (Box 35, Folder 909)
    - Goodnow, Douglas, 1939-73, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 910)
    - Gordon, Ruth, 1928-60 (Box 35, Folder 911-915)
    - Gordon, Ruth, 1961-86, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 916-920)
      With: photostat of letter from Lucille Ball, 1967 June 16
    - Gottlieb, Howard, 1956 Mar 16 (Box 36, Folder 921)
    - Gottlieb, Morton, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 922)
    - Gould, Jean, 1964-67, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 923)
    - Grasso, Ella T., 1963 Jul 29 (Box 36, Folder 924)
    - Grayson, Charles, 1944-45 (Box 36, Folder 925)
    - Gravis, Carolyn, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 926)
    - Grebanier, Bernard, 1963-68, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 927-928)
    - Green Hills Theatre, 1960-61 (Box 36, Folder 929)
    - Greene, Bert
      See: Esquire, Box 32, folder 810
    - Greene, Waldo, 1959-73, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 930-932)
    - Greene, Shirley
    - Greenwood Little Theater, 1963-67 (Box 36, Folder 933)
    - Grenfell, Gita, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 934)
    - Grey, Anthony, 1943 (Box 36, Folder 935)
    - Grieve, Christopher Murray
      See: Hugh Macdiarmid, Box 48, folder 1269
    - Group Theatre, 1932 Mar 17 (Box 36, Folder 936)
    - Grover, Dorys C., 1966-67 (Box 36, Folder 937)
    - Guarino, Piero, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 938)
    - Guillén, Jorge, 1948-49 (Box 36, Folder 939)
    - Guinan, Texas, 1939 Jun 25 (Box 36, Folder 940)
    - The Gunnery, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 941)
    - Guthrie, Tyrone, 1954-67, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 942-943)
    - Guthrie, Judith
    - "H" general, 1930-75, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 944-947)
    - H. D., 1931-35, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 948)
    - H. M. Tennent, Ltd., 1945-65 (Box 36, Folder 949-951)
    - Haas, Robert, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 952)
    - Haberman, Donald, 1959-67, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 953-955)
      With: notes by Isabel Wilder on Haberman's dissertation
    - Haeberle, Edwin, 1964-65 (Box 37, Folder 956)
    - Haight, Gordon, 1961, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 957)
    - Halline, Allan, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 958)
    - Hamalian, Leo, 1960-61 (Box 37, Folder 959)
    - Hamilton, Edith, 1943 May 11 (Box 37, Folder 960)
    - Hamish Hamilton Ltd., 1945-67 (Box 37, Folder 961)
    - Hanson, Lee David, 1962-68, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 962)
    - Hanson, Philip, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 963)
    - Harcourt, Brace & World, 1956-66 (Box 37, Folder 964)
    - Harper and Brothers, 1927-35 (Box 37, Folder 965-69)
    - Harper and Brothers, 1936-46 (Box 37, Folder 970-77)
    - Harper and Brothers, 1947 (Box 37, Folder 978-80)
    - Harper and Brothers, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 981-983)
    - Harper and Brothers, 1949-55 (Box 38, Folder 984-987)
    - Harper and Brothers, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 988-991)
    - Harper and Brothers, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 992-995)
    - Harper and Row, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 996-999)
    - Harper and Row, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 1000-1002)
    - Harper and Row, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 1003-1005)
    - Harper and Row, 1961-62 (Box 39, Folder 1006-1009)
    - Harper and Row, 1963-67 (Box 39, Folder 1010-1016)
    - Harper and Row, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 1017)
    - Harper and Row, 1969-75, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1018-1021)
    - Harris, Jed, 1931-63, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 1022-1023)
    - Harrison, Gilbert, 1965-67, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 1024)
    - Harrison, Nancy
    - Hart, John L., 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 1025)
    - Hartman, Paul, 1967-68 (Box 41, Folder 1026)
    - Harvard College Library, 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 1027)
    - Harvard University, 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 1028)
    - Harvard University Press, 1948-66 (Box 41, Folder 1029)
    - Harvey, Anthony, 1964-67 (Box 41, Folder 1030)
    - Harvey, William, 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 1031)
    - Hauschka, Ernst, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 1032)
    - Haüsmann, Klaus, 1963, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 1033)
      See also: Kiel English Seminar, Box 45, folder 1169
    - Havoc, June, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 1034)
    - Hayes, Helen, 1937-48, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 1035)
    - Haynes, Kenneth, 1935-41 (Box 41, Folder 1036)
    - Heckart, Eileen, 1975 Jun (Box 41, Folder 1037)
    - Heffelfinger, F. Peavey, 1962-77 (Box 41, Folder 1038)
    - Heit & Rothenberg, 1962-70 (Box 41, Folder 1039-1044)
    - Heit & Rothenberg, 1971-74, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 1045-1048)
      With: copies of contracts and third- party correspondence, mostly concerning a dispute over the title of an episode of "Civilisation"
    - Hellman, Lilian, 1972 Jul 31 (Box 41, Folder 1049)
    - Helmansdorfer, Urs, 1961-72 (Box 41, Folder 1050)
    - Hemingway, Ernest, 1929-31, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 1051)
    - Hemingway, Mary, 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 1052)
    - Henig, Suzanne, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1053)
    - Henriques, Lydia, 1941, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1054)
    - Henritze, Bette, 1971-74, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 1055)
    - Henry Holt & Co., 1952-67 (Box 41, Folder 1056)
    - Henry Miller's Theatre, 1920 Feb 28 (Box 41, Folder 1057)
    - Henry Regnery Co., 1951-62 (Box 41, Folder 1058)
    - Hepburn, Katherine, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 1059)
    - Herbert, Edward T., 1963 (Box 41, Folder 1060)
    - Herlihy, James L., 1967-74 (Box 41, Folder 1061)
    - Herlitschka, Herberth, 1928-60 (Box 42, Folder 1062-1070)
    - Herlitschka, Marlys
    - Herlitschka, Herberth, 1961-75, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 1071-1077)
    - Herlitschka, Marlys
    - Herlitschka, Herberth: correspondence with S. Fischer Verlag, 1951-58 (Box 42, Folder 1078-1080)
    - Herlitschka, Herberth: correspondence with S. Fischer Verlag, 1959-67 (Box 43, Folder 1081-1082)
    - Heron, Peter, 1967-69 (Box 43, Folder 1083)
    - Hersey, John, 1948 May 17 (Box 43, Folder 1084)
    - Hess, Myra, 1948 Jan 30 (Box 43, Folder 1085)
    - Heyck, Hans, 1962-66, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1086)
      Includes "German P.O.W.s at Large," outline of book proposal (?), typescript carbon
    - Heyen, Elsa, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 1087)
    - Heyward, Dorothy, 1940-41, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1088)
    - Higgins, Claire, 1962-64 (Box 43, Folder 1089)
    - [Higginson?], Sally, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1090)
    - Hiller, Wendy, 1950 Feb 11 (Box 43, Folder 1091)
    - Hills, Rust
    - Hindemith, Paul, 1959-66, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1092)
    - Hindemith, Gertrude
      Includes printed copy of Wir Bauen ein Stadt (Mainz: B. Schott's Söhne, 1930), inscribed to Wilder by Paul Hindemith, May 1960
    - Hindemith Foundation, 1965-71 (Box 43, Folder 1093)
    - Hispanic Society of America, 1957 Dec 4 (Box 43, Folder 1093a)
      See also: Oversize, Box 205, folder 4385
    - Hispanic Review
      See: Arnold Reichenberger, Box 52, folder 1460
    - Hobson, Archie, 1967-73, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1094)
    - Hobson, Eliza
    - Hofmann, Hans, 1960 (Box 43, Folder 1095)
    - Hoggson, Maclean, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 1096)
    - Hoiby, Lee, 1959 Aug 24 (Box 43, Folder 1097)
    - Holiday, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 1098)
    - Holm, Celeste, 1963 Jan (Box 43, Folder 1099)
    - Holt, Rinehart and Winston
      See: Henry Holt & Co., Box 41, folder 1056
    - Honig, Edwin, 1964 Apr 20 (Box 43, Folder 1100)
    - Hopkins, Arthur, 1919-49 (Box 43, Folder 1101)
    - Horgan, Paul, 1962-74 (Box 43, Folder 1102)
    - Horovitz, Israel, 1973-74 (Box 43, Folder 1103)
    - Horovitz, Joseph, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 1104)
    - Hospitalized Veterans' Writing Project, 1965-74 (Box 43, Folder 1105)
    - Hotaling, N. L., 1962-65 (Box 43, Folder 1106)
    - Hotson, Leslie, 1938-75, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1107)
    - Houghtaling, David, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 1108)
    - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1962-66 (Box 43, Folder 1109)
    - Houghton, Norris, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 1110)
    - Hubbard, Lydia, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1111)
    - Hudson Review, 1962-63 (Box 43, Folder 1112)
    - Hufnagel, Helga, 1953 (Box 43, Folder 1113)
    - Hunningher, Benjamin, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 1114)
    - Hunter, Mary, 1948 (Box 43, Folder 1115)
    - Hurok, Sol, 1947 Oct 23 (Box 43, Folder 1116)
    - Hurst, Fannie, 1938 Feb 7 (Box 43, Folder 1117)
    - Hutchins, Robert, 1931-75, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1118-1122)
      Includes "Address to the Graduating Class, 1935," printed
    - Hyatt, Alton, 1933-81 (Box 43, Folder 1123)
    - Hyman, Dick, 1962-67 (Box 43, Folder 1124)
    - "I" general, 1928-75 (Box 44, Folder 1125)
    - Imperatori, Edita, 1964-67 (Box 44, Folder 1126)
    - Inaugural Committee 1965
      See: Lady Bird Johnson, Box 44, folder 1150
    - Ince, Alexander, 1950 (Box 44, Folder 1127)
    - Ingalls, Jeremy, 1941 (Box 44, Folder 1128)
      With: "Rondeau for T. N. who brought me a gift of perfumes," "The Devil and Don Quixote," and a translation from Fortunatus, by Ingalls
    - Institute for Advanced Studies in the Theatre Arts, 1962-65 (Box 44, Folder 1129)
    - Institute on Man and Science
      See: Everett Clinchy, Box 29, folder 694
    - International Editors' Company, 1955-56 (Box 44, Folder 1130)
    - International Institute of Arts and Letters, 1956-62 (Box 44, Folder 1131)
      Includes certificate of membership, 1956 Dec 15
    - International Movement for Atlantic Union, 1962-66, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1132)
    - International Platform Association, 1964-65 (Box 44, Folder 1133)
    - Interpress, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 1134)
    - "J" general, 1946-74, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1135-1139)
    - Jackson, Rose, 1967-69, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1140)
    - Jacobson, Herbert, 1961-72 (Box 44, Folder 1141)
    - James, Alice, 1952-53 (Box 44, Folder 1142)
    - James, John P., 1964 (Box 44, Folder 1143)
    - James Joyce Foundation, 1967-69 (Box 44, Folder 1144)
    - James Joyce Society, 1953-73 (Box 44, Folder 1145)
    - Jameson, Frederick, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1146)
    - Jenson, Mary J., 1963 (Box 44, Folder 1147)
    - John, Karl, 1957-66 (Box 44, Folder 1148)
    - Johnson, Lamont, 1957, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 1149)
    - Johnson, Lady Bird, 1964-73 (Box 44, Folder 1150)
      Includes invitation to state dinner for Indira Gandhi, 1966
    - Johnstone, Lil Liandre, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 1151)
    - Jolas, Maria, 1940 (Box 44, Folder 1152)
    - Jones, Ernest, n.y. Aug 11 (Box 44, Folder 1153)
    - Joy, Nicholas, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1154)
    - Juth, Ema., 1928 Apr 19 (Box 44, Folder 1154a)
      Includes photographs and a copy of "A Character Sketch of My Teacher," 1910
    - "K" general, 1928-75, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1155-1157)
    - Kahler, Alice, 1971-74 (Box 44, Folder 1158)
    - Kalman, Charles, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 1159)
    - Kambestad, Dorothy, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 1160)
    - Kanin, Garson, 1953-71, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1161-1162)
      See also: Ruth Gordon, Box 35, folders 911-920
    - Kazan, Elia, 1942 Oct 18 (Box 44, Folder 1163)
    - Keedick, Lee, 1928-38 (Box 44, Folder 1164)
    - Kelley, George, 1940-49, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1165)
      With: list of books by Wilder owned by Kelley
    - Kelly, Gene, 1953 Dec 30 (Box 44, Folder 1166)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1961-62 (Box 44, Folder 1167)
    - Kerr, Walter, 1967, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1168)
    - Kerr, Jean